Prompt: british prime minister
Generated text 1: british prime minister tony blair has defended his handling of the asian tsunami disaster  saying he was not  overwhelmed  by the scale of the disaster.  the prime minister was speaking after a meeting of the g8 group of leading industrialised nations in brussels. mr blair said the disaster had been  very difficult  but he was not  overwhelmed . he said the disaster had been personal  and he hoped other premiers would too.  the meeting came as g8 ministers held their third meeting of the year to discuss the world economy and world affairs. the meeting came after mr blair said he had agreed to hold a summit of the g8 group of leading industrialised nations in the hope of averting another world recession. he said he accepted the call but said he would not accept  any compromise  on the issue.  the g8 meeting comes as g7 members attempt to hammer out a deal on debt relief for the world s poorest countries
