Prompt: good morning
Generated text 1: good morning for british music the british pop scene is celebrating its 10th anniversary this weekend  but what is so special about it all  and why are so many so many so-called great british bands still performing   is the sheer number of acts on the bill in the wee hours of the morning.   i m just here to kick start things off by having a bang with some of the best british music in the world   says jamelia  jamelia s new single  which is out now on the uk s top chart. it s called  the best british christmas album  and it s out now on 100 charts. jamelia s  which is about real people  real people  real people being real people and real people being fiction  is the band s response to a song by real people singer jamelia hayley that has become a best-selling album in the british music world. it s called 
